梅宝  就是这
There she is, Mabel--
能租到的最便宜的游乐园
The cheapest fair money can rent!
我是能省则省啊
I spared every expense!
我猜这缆车坏了
I think the sky tram is broken.
我的骨头大概也坏了
Also most of my bones.
你这家伙
This guy!
好了  好了
All right, all right.
给你们俩点事儿干
I got a job for you two.
我印了些伪造的安全检验证书
I printed up a bunch of fake safety inspection certificates.
在任何看样子可能引起法律诉讼的东西上都贴一张
Go slap one on anything that looks like a lawsuit.
斯坦叔公  这合法吗
Grunkle stan, is that legal?
只要没有警察在  什么都合法
When there's no cops around, anything's legal!
苏斯  那个打靶水池修得怎么样了
Soos, how's that dunk tank coming along?
基本快完工了  派恩斯先生
Almost ready to go, Mr. Pines.
哈  用这个能骗到一群人
Ha! You got it rigged from here to timbuktu!
谁也别想把我击下水
There's nothin' on earth that could knock me down!
是啊  除非是某种未来的激光臂大炮
Yeah, except for like a futuristic laser arm cannon.
嘿  你看到我的红色螺丝刀了吗
Hey, you haven't seen my red screwdriver, have ya?
可恶的家伙这时候不见了
Darn thing went missing.
也许它被某种神秘力量或超自然生物拿走了
Maybe some magical creature or paranormal thing took it.
喂  你是不是跟那帮小屁孩呆太久被传染了
Oy, you been spendin' too much time with those kids!
行了  我得找找我到底把那东西放哪去了
All right, let's see. Where did I put that thing?
任务正按计划实施  报告完毕
This mission is proceeding as planned. Over.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
■
时间轴： WaitinZ
翻译： Sigrid
■
校订： 萌小懒  WaitinZ
后期： WaitinZ  liloelva
怪诞小镇  第一季第九集
Gravity Falls  S01E09  Time Traveler's Pig
十二点整  水池打靶游戏开始了
It's 12:00! The dunk tank is now open!
都过来吧  来砸我吧  乡亲们
Step right up and dunk me, folks!
说你呢  牛仔短裤那个
I'm talkin' to you, cut-offs!
这就对了  大肚腩那个  高腰裤那个
That's right! Muffin top! High pants!
谁想把我砸下水
Who wants a piece of me?!
欢迎随时再来  乡亲们
Come back any time, folks!
他们怎么做成这个形状的啊
How do they get them into this shape?
太不自然了
It's unnatural.
但是  迪普  它们真的很  美味
But, Dipper, they're so... Delicious?
啊  糟了
Uh, boo!
我一会儿就来
I'll be right back.
我在这儿等你
I'll be right here!
我爱你
I love you.
看你俩啊  把整个游乐园搞得这么浪漫
Look at you two, gettin' all romantic at the fair.
哪有  这有什么的
Come on, it's no big deal.
明明就有啊
Yeah, it is.
没错  你说得对  太棒了  不是么
Okay, you're right! It is! Isn't this amazing?!
我才刚开始  我说 “嘿  你想逛逛游乐园么”
I just dove in! I said, "Hey, you wanna hang out at the fair?"
你知道她说什么吗
And you know what she said?!
嗯  可以啊
Yeah, I guess so.
嗯  可以啊  真起作用了
Yeah, I guess so! It totally worked!
你要我大胆去争取的建议  终于有效果了
All your advice about just going for it, it's finally paying off!
迪普  你什么时候才能明白呢
When are you going to learn, Dipper?
不管什么事  我总是对的
I'm always right about everything.
嘿  你闻到很浓的香体喷雾的味道没
Hey, do you smell a gallon of body spray?
嘿  你们两个蠢货有谁看到温蒂没
Hey, either of you dorks seen Wendy around?
-谁关心呢  -嘿
-Who wants to know? -Hey!
是啊  我刚买了条超级紧身裤
Yeah, I got some new super tight jeans.
我想温蒂可能想瞧瞧
Thought she might wanna check 'em out.
啊  我想起来  我在无底洞里看到她了
Yeah, you know, I think I saw her in the bottomless pit.
你真应该跳下去找她
You should really go jump in there.
可能我会的  自作聪明的蠢货
Maybe I will, smart guy.
他真是个混蛋
He is such a jerk.
是  但他是个穿紧身裤还背吉他的混蛋
Yeah, but he's a jerk with tight pants and a guitar.
不管怎样我不能让她接近温蒂
I need to keep him away from wendy at all costs.
哥  别担心  不管发生什么
Don't worry, brother, whatever happens,
小妹都会在这儿  一直支持你  每件事都
I'll be right here, supporting you ever step of--
噢  我的天啊  小猪仔
Oh, my gosh! A pig!
如果猜中了这畜生的重量
If you can guess the critter's weight,
你就可以把它带回家啦
You can take the critter home!
- 梅宝  - 它说了“梅宝”
- Mabel. - He said "Mabel"!
又或者是“门铃”
Either that or "Doorbell."
你说的是“梅宝”还是“门铃”
Did you say "Mabel" Or "Doorbell"?
梅宝
Mabel.
哦  看呐  梅宝找到她真正的孪生兄弟了
Oh, look, Mabel here found her real twin.
帕西菲卡
Pacifica!
先生  我一定要赢得那头猪仔
Sir, I must have that pig!
啊  你说“老十五”啊
Ah, old fifteen-poundy!
好  你猜它多重呢
So, how much you guessin' he weighs?
呃  十五磅
Um, 15 pounds?
你是个女巫么
Are you some kind of witch?
好吧  它归你了
Well, there's your pig.
你会需要这些的
And you'll be needin' these.
不用吗  随你便吧
No? Suit yourself.
现在一切都不一样了
Everything is different now.
哇哦  看呐
Whoa! Check it out!
我不确定那是个鸭子还是个熊猫  不过我想要一个
I don't know if it's a duck or a panda, but I want one!
我叔公教了我玩这些游戏的秘诀
My uncle taught me the secret to these games--
你冲那个工作人员的头扔
You aim for the carny's head
然后趁他迷糊的时候把奖领走
And take the prize when he's unconscious.
好主意
Nice.
给我一个球
One ball, please.
你只有一次机会
You only get one chance.
一  二  走你
And a one, and a two, and a...
噢  我的眼睛
Ow! My eye!
噢  我的天呐  噢  天啊  温蒂  你还好吗
Oh, my gosh! Oh, my gosh! Wendy, are you okay?!
我眼睛肿了吗
Does it look swollen?
没事的  别担心  我我
Everything's gonna be fine! Don't worry! I'll...
我去拿些冰来
I'll go get some ice!
她在哪儿  她在哪儿
Where is she? Where is she?
嘿  走路看着点啊你
Hey, watch where you're going, man!
好了  用冰淇淋筒敷敷你眼睛
All right, just ease your eyeball into that freezy cone.
罗比  谢谢你  你真贴心
Robbie, thanks. That's really sweet--
敷眼睛的手法还有这冰淇淋的口味
The gesture and the flavored syrup.
是吗  我只是刚好在对的时间出现在了对的地方而已
Yeah, I was just here in the right place at the right time.
你知道吗  我一直打算问你
You know, i've been meanin' to ask you...
我们经常在一起呆着
We've been spendin' a lot of time together
我在想你有没可能想跟我约会呢
And I was wondering if maybe you wanted to go out with me?
嗯  可以啊
Yeah, I guess so.
太好了
Sweet!
看呐  迪普  我赢了个小猪仔
Look, Dipper! I won my pet pig!
他叫摇摇
His name is Waddles.
因为它走路摇摇摆摆地  摇啊摇
I call him that because he waddles! Waddles!
一切都不一样了
Everything is different now.
你在看什么
What are ya lookin' at?
呃  你不走吗
Uh... Are you gonna move?
呼叫摇摇医生  我们这儿有个男孩心碎了
Paging Dr. Waddles, we got a boy here with a broken heart.
振作点  老兄  开开玩笑嘛
Come on, man, these are the jokes.
梅宝  你有没想过
Mabel, do you ever wish
能回到过去  哪怕只弥补一个错误
You could go back and undo just one mistake?
没想过  我又没做错过什么事
Nope! I do everything right all the time.
我是说  温蒂和罗比去约会
I mean, Wendy only went out
仅仅是因为罗比及时给她拿了冰块
With Robbie because he was there with the ice,
然后她需要冰块仅仅是因为被棒球打到眼睛
And she only needed ice because of the baseball,
并且我没把冰块及时送到就是因为
And I would have had the ice if it wasn't for...
那个家伙
That guy!
嗨  你  背工具腰带的  你把我的一切全毁了
Hey, you! Tool belt! You ruined my life!
啊
Huh?
少跟我装蒜  我见过你
Don't "Huh" Me! I've seen you before!
你有什么企图  你在跟踪我们吗
What's your deal? Are you following us around?
还有你为什么秃头啊  这都怎么回事
And why are you bald? What's all that about?
我的身份暴露了
My position has been compromised!
开启秘密模式  匹配周边色彩
Assuming stealth mode! Color match!
启动色彩匹配  快啊  可恶
Initiating color match! Come on! Dang it!
太神奇了  你是未来人还是什么
That's amazing! Are you from the future or something?
啊  不是  谁告诉你这些的
Uh, no! Who told you that?!
记忆抹除
Memory wipe!
这是块婴儿用纸啊
This is a baby wipe.
好吧  你们把我逼得走投无路了
All right, you've cornered me.
我是个时光穿梭者
I'm a time traveler.
等一下  如果你是来自未来
So wait a minute, if you're from the future,
那你有时光机之类的东西吗
Do you have, like, a time machine or something?
是有那么个东西
That's kinda how that works.
能借我吗
Could I borrow it?
别那么小气  时光机借我  就只用一次
Come on! Can I use your time machine just once?
这根本没门  看  这是高度灵敏
Out of the question! You know this is sensitive,
极为复杂的时光机器
Extremely complicated time equipment!
它看起来像卷尺
It looks like a tape measure.
闭上你的嘴
You shut your time-mouth!
你觉得这是真的吗
This makin' any sense to you?
我觉得他疯了
I think he's just crazy.
噢  你们竟然不相信我
Oh, you don't believe me?
猜我刚才去哪儿了
Guess where I was!
没错  十五年前此处是一家戏服店
That's right, 15 years ago there was a costume store right here!
马上就来
One second!
噢  见鬼  熄
Aw, heck! Pat!
- 熄灭  - 那个  你是谁来着
- Pat down! - So who are you again?
布伦丁・布兰丁  时光异常移除员  来自207012年
Blendin Blandin, time anomaly removal crew, year 20-snyeventy-12!
（注：那不是个7，鼻音化了）
我的任务是阻止一系列的时间异常现象
My mission is to stop a series of time anomalies
这些异常应该就在此处发生了
That are supposed to happen at this very location!
但是  我没发现任何异常迹象啊
B-but I don't see any anomalies!
我不知道这是不是某种悖论
I don't know if it's some kind of paradox
又或者是我太累了
Or if I'm just really tired!
看起来你可能需要休息一下
You know, you sound like you could use a break.
绝对需要  绝对需要
Definitely. Definitely.
推荐你去玩玩
Might we recommend one of
这个神秘游乐园各种各样的项目
The various attractions at the mystery fair?
你猜我怎么想的  管它呐
You know what? What the heck!
我绝对得去玩玩
I'm worth it!
但我会盯着你们的
But I got my eye on you!
- 一个人  - 呃  不好意思  哥们儿
- One, please! - Aw, sorry, dude,
你得把你的腰带取了才能坐上去
But you're gonna have to take your belt off for the ride.
你腰带上的东西可能会飞出来打到别的东西
One of your tools might fly off and accidently fix something.
请千万千万保管好它
Guard it with your life!
哥们放心  我会像雄鹰一样守护好它
I will watch it like a hawk, dude.
如鹰一般
Like a hawk!
就是这个东西  梅宝
Here it is, Mabel--
我们回到历史任一时刻的入场券
Our ticket to any moment in history!
我们去抓两只渡渡鸟来  然后让它们亲热
Lets go get two dodos and force them to make out!
不行  我们得谨慎一点
No! We gotta be smart about this.
那些有关悖论的话让我有点懵
All that paradox talk kinda freaked me out.
我要做的只是回去  然后弥补我的过失
All I'm gonna do is go back and fix my one mistake.
如果我没把球扔偏
If I don't miss that baseball throw,
我就不会打到温蒂的眼睛  然后罗比就不会安抚她
I won't hit Wendy in the eye, and Robbie won't comfort her,
他们就不会开始约会了
And they won't start going out.
我也要去  我要重温我生命中最美好的那个时刻
I'm coming, too! I wanna relive the greatest moment of my life--
赢得摇摇的时刻
Winning Waddles!
待会儿见
See ya later.
我们早些见  耶  耶  耶
See you earlier! Yuck, yuck, yuck!
十二点整  水池打靶游戏开始了
It's 12:00! The dunk tank is now open!
都过来吧  来砸我吧  乡亲们
Step right up and dunk me, folks!
说你呢  牛仔短裤那个
I'm talkin' to you, cut-offs!
重来一遍
Do-over?
Do-over!
如果你能猜中  - 十五磅
If you can guess-- fifteen pounds!
还有  是的  我是个女巫
And yes, I am a witch.
好吧  是时候聚集起人群了
Well, time to round up a mob.
嗨  温蒂  你来了
Hey, Wendy. There you are.
嘿  你的帽子怎么搞的
Hey, what happened to your hat?
呃  没什么  嘿  看  那是什么啊
Uh, nothing. Hey, look! What's that?
喔哦  去看看
Whoa! Check it out!
我不确定那是个鸭子还是个熊猫  不过我想要一个
I don't know if it's a duck or a panda, but I want one!
一个球  谢谢
One ball, please.
你只有一次机会
You only get one chance.
那是你才这么想
That's what you think.
熊猫鸭一个  马上到手
One panda-duck, coming right up!
冷静  迪普  第二次机会  别搞砸了
Okay, Dipper, second chance. Don't mess this up.
打中了
Yes!
噢  我的眼睛
Ow! My eye!
怎么会这样
What?!
眼睛肿了吗
Does it look swollen??
奇了怪了
That's so weird.
哦  嘿  罗比
Oh, hey, Robbie.
怎么说呢  我们也做了很久的玩伴了
So anyway, we've been hangin' out a lot,
我一直在想你有没可能想跟我约会呢
And i've been wondering if, uh, you wanted to go out with me?
嗯  可以啊
Yeah, I guess so.
太好了
Sweet!
一模一样的事情发生两遍  太奇怪了
The exact same thing happened twice! It was spooky!
喔  也许这是个时间魔咒
Ooh, maybe it's a time curse!
摇摇猪  你会说“时间魔咒”吗
Waddles, can you say "Time curse"?
你的脸肉嘟嘟的
Your face is so fat!
难道时间的力量能够
Is it possible that the forces of time
自然地使得事情的新发展被撤消
Naturally conspire to undo any new outcomes?
不行  不行  我得再试一遍
No, no. I just need to try again.
第三次定会上演好戏
Third time's the charm.
能有多难啊
How hard can it be?
给我找到那个女巫
Find the witch!
噢  我的眼睛
Ow! My eye!
嘿  你还好吧
Hey, are you all right?
啊  噢  我的眼睛
Aah! Ow! My eye!
噢  真倒霉
Oh, bad luck.
呃  温蒂  你很迫切地想要得到那个动物玩偶吗
Uh, Wendy? How badly do you want that stuffed animal thing?
比世界上任何一个东西都想要  迪普
More than anything in the world, Dipper.
那好吧
Okay.
我爱死我的猪仔了
I love my pig!
如果我根据风速调整球向
If I adjust the ball for wind speed...
也把棉花糖列入考虑因素
Factoring cotton candy...
坦然面对吧  迪普  显然你是命中注定
Face it, Dipper, you're obviously fated
在游乐园这天走霉运
To have a bad day at the fair.
就像我和我的摇摇注定在一起一样
Just like I'm fated to be with waddles!
貌似我漏了一个变量
It's like there's one variable missing.
什么是变量
What's a variable?
哈  搞定了
Ha! That's it!
我想到制胜的方法了  不会打到温蒂
I figured out a way to win the toss, not hit Wendy,
同时也能阻止温蒂和罗比去约会
And stop Wendy and Robbie from going out!
真了不起  我要再去赢一次我的猪猪
Awesome! I'm gonna go win my pig again!
喂  喂  喂  你不能走  我的计划需要你啊
Whoa, whoa, whoa! You can't leave. I need you for my plan.
那摇摇怎么办呢
But what about Waddles?
几分钟就搞定了  我们走
It'll just take a few minutes! Let's go!
可以开始了吧
You gonna go, man?
一  二  走
And a one, and a two, and a...
噢  兄弟  你扔偏了
Aw, dude, you missed.
你再看看
Did I?
美女  你的不明物种填充玩偶
Your stuffed creature of indeterminate species, miss.
噢  太棒了
Oh, awesome!
温蒂  你在这儿啊  嗨  罗比
There you are, Wendy. Hi, Robbie.
我在想你是否  呃  你
So I was wondering if, uh, you--
看  迪普送给我的
Look what Dipper got for me!
懒得看  我都说不出这是个啥  真蠢
Whatever. Can't even tell what species it is. Stupid.
他怎么搞的
What's his deal?
貌似我来游乐园找对了伙伴
Looks like I came to the fair with the right guy!
大赢家诞生
We have a winner!
随时乐意效劳  兄弟
Anytime, broseph.
我要去赢我的猪猪咯
Now to win my pig.
它归你了  别人没机会了
It's all yours! No one else's!
“老十五”  你终身享有咯
Old fifteen-poundy! Yours forever!
第三圈真是更刺激了
That was even more awesome the third time around!
漏斗蛋糕  迪普  我们去吃吧
Funnel cake! Let's go get some, Dipper!
怎么了
What's w--
梅宝  怎么
Mabel, what--
我等你叫完吧
I'll just wait until you're done.
叫完了  好  发生什么事了
I'm done. Okay, what is wrong?
我们把时间都搞乱了
We messed up the timeline!
帕西菲卡看到了小广告
Pacifica saw the flier
而且抢在我前面把摇摇赢走了
And won Waddles before I did!
她把摇摇抢走了  迪普
She took Waddles, Dipper!
噢  梅宝  我很抱歉
Oh, mabel, I'm sorry.
也还好  我们只要再回去重来一遍就好了
It's okay, we just need to go back and do things differently.
等等  梅宝  你想想  我精心计算了
Mabel, wait! Look, I did the math--
再换个时间的话  温蒂最终会和罗比约会
In any other timeline, Wendy ends up going out with Robbie!
我不能再一次把今天搞砸了
I can't mess this day up again!
但如果我们不回去  我就会永远地失去摇摇
But if we don't go, then i'll lose Waddles forever!
嘿
Hey!
还给我
Give it back!
我们在什么年代
When are we?
问题的关键是  我们在什么年代
The real question is, when are we?
噢  等一下  你刚刚是不是已经
Oh, wait, did you already--
- 对  我已经  - 因为我也准备--
- Yeah, I already-- - 'cause I was gonna--
- 是啊  是啊  一样  - 好吧
- Yeah. Yeah, same thing. - All right.
你听到没
Do you hear that?
旅客们  注意提防山里的狮子啊
Be on the look out for mountain lions, travelers!
谁想拉稀  谁想拉稀吗
Dysentery? Who wants dysentery?
继续前进  强壮的牛儿们
Forge ahead, mighty oxen!
为了俄勒冈之路上等待我们的崭新生活
For a new life awaits us on this Oregon trail!
我们在哪啊  七十年代吗
Where are we? The '70s?
你把我们送回到一百五十年前了  真是神童啊
You sent us back 150 years, genius!
这是开拓者们的时代
It's pioneer times!
别吓我  佛蒂利亚
By trembly! Fertilla,
我怎么听着像你又生了两个孩子
It seems you've given birth to two more children!
似乎是的  又多了两双小手帮忙提炼油脂
It appears I have. More little hands to render the tallow.
油脂  什么东西
Tallow? What?
妈妈  她的嘴里都是银色的东西
Her mouth is filled with silver, mother!
这叫作牙套
These are called braces.
梅宝  我们不能跟过去纠缠不清啊
Mabel, we can't start messing with the past!
噢  那又是谁总一天到晚
Oh, says the guy who messed
跟过去纠缠不清  还害我损失了我的猪仔
With the past all day, and cost me my pig?
我想怎么捣乱就怎么捣乱
I'll mess with whatever I want!
快瞧瞧  神奇的按键机器
Check it out! A magic button machine!
可以闪光的鞋子
Shoes that blink!
嗨  大姐  猜猜未来谁有选举权
Hey, sister, guess who gets to vote in the future?
女士们  手举高
Ladies! Up top!
这个叫做击掌  可以教教你的朋友们
That's called a high-five. Teach it to your friends.
把东西给我  我要重新设定时间轴
Give me that! I'm gonna set the timeline right!
嘿  不要啊
Hey! No!
快跑  掩护
Run! Take cover!
来了
It's coming!
未来太炫了
This future seems neat.
我来啦  摇摇
I'm coming, Waddles!
嘿
Hey!
我看到了  我又看到了
I seen it! I seen it again!
好了  不说我了
But enough about me.
注意看  又一个我
Behold... Me!
这东西开始发烫了
This thing is getting hotter!
烫  烫  烫  烫
Hot! Hot, hot, hot!
- 你干嘛了  - 我也不知道啊
- What did you do?! - I don't know!
我们在哪儿
Where are we?
一片漆黑  什么也看不到
It's nothing but inky blackness for miles!
梅宝  你还没意识到吗  我们被传送到时间的尽头了
Mabel, don't you see? We've transported to the end of time!
等一下  这里怎么这么臭啊
Wait, why does it smell so bad in here?
看呐  我们又回到现代了
Look! We're back in the present!
但是是现代的什么时候啊
But which present?
这是我得到的最好的礼物了  太棒了
This is the best present ever! Yes!
不  把那东西给我
No! Give me that thing!
迪普  还给我
Dipper, give it back!
够了  梅宝  都结束了  你放弃吧
Look, Mabel, it's over, okay? Give it up!
我费了那么大的工夫  绝不能再失去了
I've worked too hard to lose this!
那摇摇怎么办  他是我灵魂伴侣啊
But what about Waddles? He was my soul mate!
你都说了一万次了
You said that about a ball of yarn once!
你真的希望看到温蒂和罗比约会吗
Do you really want Wendy to date Robbie?
我也不知道啊
I don't know.
你不会让我有负罪感的  梅宝  这次没戏
You're not guilt-tripping me, Mabel. Not this time.
别不高兴啦  梅宝  我了解你的
Come on, Mabel, I know you.
过了今天你就会把这事抛在脑后
You're gonna forget about this in a day.
来  嘿  我证明给你看
Here! Hey, i'll prove it!
看
See?
好吧  也许你能在一周内忘了这件事
Okay, maybe you'll forget in a week.
一个月  一个月内她会好起来的
A month. She'll be better in a month!
摇摇  摇摇
Waddles. Waddles.
现在看你们的左边  你们会看到痛不欲生的梅宝
And if you look to your left, you'll see miserable Mabel--
这孩子自从她的梦想被某个没心没肺的坏小子
The girl who went bonkers after
粉碎之后  就开始在这儿撞木桩
Her dreams were shattered by some heartless jerk.
噢  嘿  迪普
Oh, hey, Dipper!
我不确定这是个鸭子还是个熊猫  但我想要一个
I don't know if it's a duck or a panda, but I want one.
温蒂  我只是想说
Wendy, I just wanted to say that...
那个  我只是想说  人时常会犯错
Well, I just wanted to say that people make mistakes,
当人们犯错的时候  你应该原谅他们
And when they do, you should forgive them.
还有就是  那条紧身裤没那么好
And also, that tight pants are overrated.
哥们儿  你把我绕晕了
Dude, you lost me.
我知道
I know.
一个球  谢谢
One ball, please.
你只有一次机会
You only get one chance.
一  二  走
And a one, and a two, and a...
噢  我的眼睛
Ow! My eye!
嘿  温蒂  你没事吧
Hey, Wendy, are you okay?
来得正好  我正好有点事要问你
You know, this is the perfect time for me to ask you something.
完了
It is done.
迪普  谢谢  谢谢  谢谢  谢谢
Dipper! Thank you! Thank you! Thank you! Thank you!
谢谢
Thank you.
他在用小猪语说“谢谢你”
He's saying "Thank you" in pig!
是吧  摇摇
Aren't you, Waddles?
我实在没法让你伤心  梅宝
I couldn't break your heart, Mabel.
另外  温蒂也不可能和罗比一整个夏天都约会  是吧
Besides, there's no way Wendy can date Robbie all summer, right?
你俩
You two!
你们清楚你们刚违反了多少规则吗
Do you have any idea how many rules you just broke?!
我是在问你们  我刚才可没跟你们俩在一起
I'm asking, I wasn't there with you.
肯定不少  是不是
It was probably a lot, right?
布伦丁・布兰丁
Blendin Blandin!
时间悖论规避强执特遣队
The time paradox avoidance enforcement squadron!
没错  我们的电话一直响个不停
That's right, and our phones have been ringing off the hook.
十九世纪有居民击掌
There's settlers high-fiving in the 1800s
计算器流窜到了八个世纪以前
And calculators littered through eight centuries!
由于违背了时光穿梭者的行为准则
You are under arrest for violations
你被逮捕了
of the time travelers code of conduct.
都是那些小鬼们干的
It was those kids!
还有他们的头儿  摇摇
And their leader, Waddles!
那只是头猪  布伦丁
That's a pig, Blendin.
噢  我会报复你们的
Oh! I'll get you for this!
我要回到过去  让你们爸妈一辈子碰不着面
I'll go back in time and make sure your parents never meet!
我们不还在这儿嘛
Well, we're still here.
我猜他把那事搞忘了
Guess he forgot to go back.
哈  你们这些笨蛋
Ha! You suckers!
我安然无恙地坐在这儿  然而你们却口袋空空了
Your pockets are empty and I'm still sitting high and dry!
尽管喝倒彩吧  我就喜欢这感觉
Yeah, boo! Boo! I love it!
嘿  肌肉猛男们  对  说你呐  酷发哥
Hey, biceps! Yeah, I'm talking to you, haircut!
让的你们小宇宙爆发吧
Take your best shot!
我觉得我们永远都不会知道布伦丁要找的那些
So I guess we never found out who was causing
时光异常现象是谁造成的了
Those time anomalies Blendin was looking for.
等等  梅宝  我认为是我们造成的
Wait, Mabel... I think it was us.
呃  我脑袋疼
Ugh, my brain hurts.
噢  老天  不会让我一整个夏天都忍受这种画面吧
Aw, jeez, I gotta deal with this all summer?
这个很好吃的  焦糖酱哦
It's good. It's caramel.
交给我了
I'm on it.
我的紧身裤啊  缩水了
My pants! They're shrinking!
噢  天呐
Oh, man.
这个可以有  猪猪
That'll do, pig.
这个可以有
That'll do.
你违反了宇宙时间的永恒之律
You have broken the eternal laws of space-time.
求你大发慈悲  时光宝宝
I beg your mercy, time baby!
现在你必须去清理所有的时光异常现象
You now must clean up all of the anomalies.
我是老人麦戈科特  本地怪人一枚
Old man McGuckett, local kook!
蜡像有生命吗
Are the wax figures alive?
你看什么看
What are you looking at?